ILGWU David Dubinsky Correspondence 5780/002
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Southeastern Region, 1955-1961 (Box 363, Folder 1a-1f)
- Southeastern Region, 1953-1954 (Box 363, Folder 2a-2c)
  I.c.w. John S. Martin.
- Southeastern Region, 1951-1952 (Box 364, Folder 1a-1b)
- Southeastern Region, 1949-1950 (Box 364, Folder 2a-2b)
- Southeastern Region, 1947-1948 (Box 364, Folder 3a-3b)
- Southeastern Region. Alix of Miami, 1963-1965 (Box 364, Folder 4)
- Southeastern Region, 1954 (Box 364, Folder 5)
  Bien Jolie. (Dunn, No. Car., Scranton, Pa.)
- Southeastern Region. Biflex Foundation. Inc., 1948-1955 (Box 364, Folder 6a-6d)
  Corres. w. E.T. Kehrer & Union officers; Union releases for Biflex workers; newspaper clippings.
- Southeastern Region. Cotton City Frocks, 1948-1966 (Box 365, Folder 1a-1b)
  (N.E.) Corres. w. John S. Martin & E. T. Kehrer re Cotton City Mfg. Co., incl. correspondence. re strikes, strike fund, & agreement w. Union.
- Southeastern Region. Ely-Walker Dry Goods, Inc., 1951-1956 (Box 365, Folder 2)
  (S.W.) I.c.w. Meyer Perlstein on negotiations w. firm.
- Southeastern Region. Exquisite Forms. See Upper South Dept. (Box 365, Folder 2a)
- Southeastern Region. G.H. and E. Freydberg (Local 91)., 1954-1955 (Box 365, Folder 3a-3c)
- Southeastern Region. Glendale Mfg. Co. (Ashville, S.C., Fall River, Mass.), 1955 (Box 365, Folder 4)
- Southeastern Region. Hazelhurst Mfg. Co., 1955 (Box 365, Folder 5)
  (E.O.T.)
- Southeastern Region. Undergarment Corp., 1956 (Box 365, Folder 6)
- Southeastern Region. Jackson Gmt. Co. Cotton Shops, Inc., 1953-1955 (Box 365, Folder 7)
  (Chicago, Ill.)
- Southeastern Region. Kanner Dress Co., 1953 (Box 365, Folder 8)
  (E.O.T.) Letters bet. John Martin (S.E. Director) & Israel Horowitz (Gen. Mgr.), E.O.T. Dept.
- Southeastern Region. Kayser-Roth, Inc., 1959 (Box 365, Folder 9a-9b)
  Corres. w. Kehrer re negotiations; incl. proposals.
- Southeastern Region. Lamar Mfg. Co. (Orange, N.J.), 1955 (Box 365, Folder 10)
- Southeastern Region. Lucky Star Jeans Juvenile Mfg. (Tupelo, Miss., San Antonio, Texas), 1954-1955 (Box 365, Folder 11)
- S.E. Modern Globe, 1953-1954 (Box 366, Folder 1)
  See Midwest.
- S.E. Movie Star Slip, Inc. (Purvis, Poplarville, Miss.), 1955-1963 (Box 366, Folder 2)
- S.E. Munsingwear, Inc., 1954-1957 (Box 366, Folder 3)
  (Hominy, Okla., Minneapolis, Minn.) Incl. agreements.
- S.E. Nachman and Son, Inc., 1953-1954 (Box 366, Folder 4)
  (Philadelphia, Pa., So. Car.)
- S.E. Oneita Knitting Mills, 1954-1964 (Box 366, Folder 5a-5b)
  (Utica, N.Y., Andrews, S.C.)
- S.E. Perfection Garment Co. See Upper South. (Box 366, Folder 5c)
- S.E. Portrait Frocks, Inc., 1949-1956 (Box 366, Folder 6)
  (Lebanon, Ky., Walterboro, S.C.)
- S.E. Rhea Mfg. Co., 1954-1958 (Box 366, Folder 7)
  (Bainbridge, Ga., Milwaukee, Wisc.)
- S.E. Rhoda Lee, Inc., 1963 (Box 366, Folder 8)
  (Elberton, Ga., Mt. Carmel, Pa.)
- S.E. Rivoli Mills, 1951-1954 (Box 366, Folder 9)
  (Chattanooga, Tenn.)
- S.E. Serbin, Inc., 1955 (Box 366, Folder 10a-10c)
  (Cleveland, Miami, Fayetteville, Tenn.) Corres. w. Kehrer & Morris Glushein re organizational & strike activities in Miami & Fayetteville.
- S.E. Sherman Mfg. Co., 1955 (Box 367, Folder 1)
  (Orange, N.J.)
- S.E. Staff, 1954-1963 (Box 367, Folder 2a-2c)
  Corres. w. Kehrer & officers of S.E. Dept. re internal Union situations (officers who resigned or were dismissed, individuals joining staff, & reports on officers by Kehrer).
- S.E. Stardust, 1956 (Box 367, Folder 3)
  (Poughkeepsie, N.Y.)
- S.E. Watertown Undergarment Corp., 1956 (Box 367, Folder 4)
- S.E. Wm. Carter Co., 1951-1959 (Box 367, Folder 5)
  See N.E. Dept.
- Southwestern Region, 1957-1959 (Box 367, Folder 6)
  Sept. 1957-59. (Changed name to Central States Region, July 1, 1958.) I.c.w. Frederick Siems; letters from officers of Locals proposing Fran Rother for Director, Sept. 1957.
- S.W., 1953-1957 (Box 367, Folder 7a-7d)
  1953, Aug. 1957. I.c.w. Meyer Perlstein; Union pamphlets & broadsides for workers to unionize; list of non-union shops in S.W. area (1952).
- S.W., 1947-1952 (Box 367, Folder 8a-8c)
- S.W. Ritmor Sportswear, Ind., 1951-1956 (Box 368, Folder 1)
  (Also W. Helena Garment Co., Arkansas.) Corres. re negotiations.
- S.W. Seamprufe, Inc., 1949-1957 (Box 368, Folder 2a-2b)
  (Also in N.E.) I.c.w. M. Perlstein on strike activities & negotiations w. firm; Union pamphlets & broadsides.
- S.W. Staff, 1948-1958 (Box 368, Folder 3a-3c)
- S.W. Strutwear, Inc., 1953-1954 (Box 368, Folder 4)
  (Minneapolis, Minn., Clarksdale, Miss.) Incl. jurisdictional dispute w. the American Federation of Hosiery Workers.
- S.W. Western Garment Co., 1947-1953 (Box 368, Folder 5)
  I.c.w. Meyer Perlstein on negotiations.
- Lower Southwest Region, 1955-1958 (Box 368, Folder 6)
  I.c.w. Sol C. Chaikin.
- Upper South Dept., 1962-1966 (Box 368, Folder 7a-7b)
  Incl. letters from Angela Bambace.
- Upper South Dept., 1948-1961 (Box 369, Folder 1a-1c)
  Corres. w. Angela Bambace on organizational activities & negotiations w. firms; recommendations & resolutions adopted at conference of the Upper South Dept., 1952
- U.S. Exquisite Forms, 1953-1957 (Box 369, Folder 2)
  (Also S.E.)
- U.S. Golden Hill, 1956 (Box 369, Folder 3)
  (Also Eastern-out-of-Town.)
- U.S. Keller-Kohn, Inc., Baltimore, Md., 1953-1954 (Box 369, Folder 4a-4b)
  Corres. w. N. Kirtzman, Charles Kreindler, Philip Dupkin (Chairman of Bd., Keller-Kohn) on organizational activities in Cleveland strike, agreements.
- U.S. Kenrose Mfg. Co., 1959-1962 (Box 369, Folder 5a-5c)
  Corres. w. Bambace re strike & negotiations; incl. D.D. statement on Kenrose strike, June 8, 1960, & notes.
- U.S. Maidenform, Inc., 1953-1966 (Box 369, Folder 6)
  (Also E.O.T.)
- U.S. Perfection Garment Co., 1953-1957 (Box 370, Folder 1)
  (S.E., O.-Ky.)
- Western States Region, Mode O'Day, 1946-1966 (Box 370, Folder 2a-2d)
  Corres. w. Louis Levy (Director), Pacific Coast area, Elias Lieberman & Mode O'Day negotiations of agreements.
- Releases, 1962-1965 (Box 370, Folder 3)
- Requests. A, 1958-1964 (Box 371, Folder 1)
  I.c.w. American Arbitration Association.
- Requests. A., 1957-1964 (Box 371, Folder 2)
  I.c.w. American Cancer Society, 1958-64. American Civil Liberties Union, 1957-64.
- Requests. A., 1959-1966 (Box 371, Folder 3)
  I.c.w. American Council for Emigres in the Professions, Inc., 1961-66. American Council for Nationalities Service, 1959-66.
- Requests. A., 1958-1965 (Box 371, Folder 4)
  I.c.w. American Friends of Hebrew University.
- Requests. A. (Box 371, Folder 5)
- Requests. A. (Box 371, Folder 6)
- Requests. A., 1958-1964 (Box 371, Folder 7)
  I.c.w. American University.
- Requests. A., 1960-1965 (Box 371, Folder 8)
  I.c.w. Arthritis Foundation.
- Requests. B. (Box 372, Folder 1)
- Requests. B., 1964-1967 (Box 372, Folder 2)
  I.c.w. Boys' Club of America.
- Requests. C., 1954-1967 (Box 372, Folder 3)
  I.c.w. Catholic Charities.
- Requests. C. (Box 372, Folder 4)
- Requests. C., 1952-1959 (Box 372, Folder 5)
  I.c.w. Commentary.
- Requests. C. (Box 372, Folder 6)
- Requests. C. (Box 372, Folder 7)
- Requests. C., 1958-1965 (Box 372, Folder 8)
  I.c.w. Conference on Economic Progress.
- Requests. C., 1956-1966 (Box 372, Folder 9a-9b)
  I.c.w. Council of the Golden Ring Clubs.
- Requests. D. (Box 373, Folder 1)
- Requests. D. Eugene V. Debs Foundation, 1962-1966 (Box 373, Folder 2)
- Requests. D. (Box 373, Folder 3)
- Requests. E. (Box 373, Folder 4)
- Requests. F. I.d.. Fair Campaign Practices Committee, 1959-1965 (Box 373, Folder 5)
- Requests. F. Incl. Foreign Policy Assoc., 1937-1966 (Box 373, Folder 6)
- Requests. F. Freedom House, 1960-1964 (Box 373, Folder 7)
- Requests. F. Freedom House, 1952-1960 (Box 373, Folder 8)
- Requests. G., 1958-1965 (Box 374, Folder 1a-1b)
  I.c.w. Golden Age Clubs.
- Requests. G., 1953-1965 (Box 374, Folder 1c-1d)
  I.c.w. Greater New York Fund, 1953-65; Greater N.Y. Safety Council, 1958-63.
- Requests. H., 1952-1966 (Box 374, Folder 1e-1g)
  Heart Assoc., American, 1964-65. Hope, 1959-66. I.c.w. Henry A. Kissinger on Harvard International Seminar, 1952.
- Requests. I. (Box 374, Folder 2)
- Requests. J. (Box 374, Folder 3a-3b)
- Requests. J. (Box 374, Folder 4)
- Requests. K. (Box 375, Folder 1)
- Requests. L., 1934-1964 (Box 375, Folder 2a-2c)
  I.c.w. Labor Aid Project, 1953-64; Labor Temple Fellowship, 1957-59; League for Industrial Democracy, 1934-64.
- Requests. L., 1955-1965 (Box 375, Folder 3a-3b)
  Lower East Side Neighborhood Assoc.
- Requests. M., 1953-1957 (Box 375, Folder 4a-4b)
  I.c.w. Moral Rearmament.
- Requests. N., 1952-1965 (Box 375A, Folder 1)
  I.c.w. National Advisory Comm. on Farm Labor, 1958-65; National Assoc. for the Advancement of Colored People, 1952-65.
- Requests. N. (Box 375A, Folder 2)
- Requests. N., 1958-1965 (Box 375A, Folder 3)
  Incl. National Comm. Against Discrimination in Housing.
- Requests. N., 1952-1963 (Box 375A, Folder 4)
  I.c.w. Nat'l. Committee for Labor Israel.
- Requests. N. (Box 375A, Folder 5)
- Requests. N. (Box 375A, Folder 6)
- Requests. N. (Box 375A, Folder 7)
- Requests. N. (Box 375A, Folder 8)
- Requests. N. Nat'l. Urban League, 1954-1965 (Box 375B, Folder 1)
- Requests. N. (Box 375B, Folder 2)
  I.c.w. Nat'l. Urban League.
- Requests. N. New School for Social Research, 1952-1965 (Box 375B, Folder 3)
- Requests. N. (Box 375B, Folder 4)
- Requests. N. (Box 375B, Folder 5)
- Requests. N. (Box 375B, Folder 6)
- Requests. N., 1959-1965 (Box 375B, Folder 7)
  I.c.w. N.Y. University Medical Center.
- Requests. N. (Box 375B, Folder 8)
- Requests. O. (Box 375B, Folder 9)
- Requests. P., 1957-1964 (Box 375B, Folder 10a-10b)
  I.c.w. Police Athletic League.
- Requests. R. (Box 375C, Folder 1)
- Requests. R. Eleanor Roosevelt Memorial Foundation, 1960-1964 (Box 375C, Folder 2a-2c)
  Labor's Drive, Collections & Corres.
- Requests. R., 1962-1965 (Box 375C, Folder 3)
  I.c.w. Roosevelt University.
- Requests. S. (Box 375C, Folder 4)
- Requests. S., 1955-1963 (Box 375C, Folder 5)
  I.c.w. Society for the Rehabilitation of the Facially Disfigured.
- Requests. S., 1957-1966 (Box 375C, Folder 6)
  Southern Christian Leadership Conference; I.c.w. Martin Luther King, Jr., 1958-66; Southern Regional Council, 1957-63.
- Requests. S. (Box 375D, Folder 1)
- Requests. S., 1954-1959 (Box 375D, Folder 2)
  I.c.w. Louis Stark Memorial Fund.
- Requests. S. Sanatoriums (and hospitals), (also in General Requests) (Box 375D, Folder 3a-3f)
  I.c.w. City of Hope, Hebrew Hospital for the Chronic Sick, Jewish Consumptive Relief Society, Jewish Chronic Disease Hospital.
- Requests. S. Sanatoriums (Box 375E, Folder 1a-1c)
  I.c.w. Memorial Center for Cancer & Allied Diseases.
- Requests. T. (Box 375E, Folder 2)
- Requests. U., 1953-1965 (Box 375E, Folder 3a-3c)
  I.c.w. United Jewish Appeal, 1959-65; United Negro College Fund, 1953-65.
- Requests. V. (Box 375E, Folder 4)
- Requests. W., 1953-1965 (Box 375F, Folder 1)
  I.c.w. Weizmann Institute of Science.
- Requests. W. (Box 375F, Folder 2)
- Requests. W. Workers Defense League, 1950-1960 (Box 375F, Folder 3)
- Requests. W. Workmen's Circle, School, Chorus, 1940-1965 (Box 375F, Folder 4)
- Requests. W. (Box 375F, Folder 5)
  Incl. Workmen's Circle.
- Requests. Y. (Box 375F, Folder 6)
- Requests. Y. (Box 375F, Folder 7)
  I.c.w. Yivo Institute for Jewish Research.
- Requests. Z. (Box 375F, Folder 8)
- Requests. Special Cases. Surnames G and H (Box 375F, Folder 9)
  Corres. w. names A-F, I-Z unavailable.
- Retirement Fund. See ILGWU Social Insurance Programs. (Box 376, Folder 1)
- Roosevelt, Eleanor, 1938-1965 (Box 376, Folder 2a-2d)
  Corres. w. Eleanor Roosevelt on 1940 politics- A.L.P. & Liberal Party-routine messages; letters from Sidney Glazier (Producer), "The Roosevelt Story," 1965. (29 letters from Eleanor Roosevelt)
- Eleanor Roosevelt Cancer Foundation, 1962-1965 (Box 376, Folder 3a-3b)
  Incl. reports on cancer research projects, minutes of Bd. of Governors; meetings; resolutions & letters from Sidney Glazier (Exec. Dir.) & James Roosevelt (President).
- Eleanor Roosevelt Cancer Foundation, 1959-1961 (Box 376, Folder 4a-4c)
  Same as above; AFL-CIO drive on implementing program.
- Franklin D. Roosevelt Foundation, 1947-1965 (Box 377, Folder 1a-1d)
  Letters from Foundation on activities, incl. financial statement of Foundation; progress reports; minutes.
- Franklin Delano Roosevelt Memorial Commission, 1962-1965 (Box 377, Folder 2)
  Incl. letters from Francis Biddle (Chairman) re activities.
- Roosevelt University, Chicago, 1945-1961 (Box 377, Folder 3a-3c)
  Incl. letters from Edward J. Sparling, (President); establishment of the Wm. Green Memorial Library & Union contributions.
- S-Sh, 1962-1966 (Box 378, Folder 1a-1b)
- S-Sh, 1951-1961 (Box 378, Folder 2a-2c)
  Incl. article on D.D. in Saturday Evening Post; "Dictator in Sheep's Clothing;" responses to article, Nov. 1949.
- Si, 1962-1966 (Box 378, Folder 3a-3b)
- Si, 1952-1961 (Box 378, Folder 4a-4c)
- Schlesinger, Emil, 1950-1961 (Box 379, Folder 1a-1b)
  Letters on legal matters, incl. publication, "A Summary & Critique of the Law of Picketing in New York" by Emil Schlesinger, 1953.
- Settlements, 1964 (Box 379, Folder 3)
- Settlements, 1963 (Box 379, Folder 4)
- Settlements, 1962 (Box 379, Folder 5)
- Settlements, 1961 (Box 379, Folder 6)
- Settlements, 1960 (Box 379, Folder 7)
- Settlements, 1957-1959 (Box 379, Folder 8a-8b)
- Settlements, 1955-1956 (Box 380, Folder 1a-1b)
- Settlements, 1954 (Box 380, Folder 2a-2b)
- Settlements, 1952-1953 (Box 380, Folder 3a-3b)
  June 1952-53.
- Settlements, 1951-1952 (Box 380, Folder 4)
  1951- June 1952.
- Shorter Work Week, 1965 (Box 380, Folder 5a)
- Signature of 450,000, 1965 (Box 380, Folder 5b)
  Thank-you letters for publication.
- Silverstein, Charles M., Executive Asst. to the Mayor, 1961-1964 (Box 380, Folder 6)
- Sixtieth Anniversary of Union., 1960 (Box 380, Folder 7)
  Aug. 1960. Incl. congratulatory messages; N.Y. Times editorial & New Leader on anniversary.
- Speaking invitations. A. (Box 381, Folder 1a-1b)
- Speaking Invitations. B. (Box 381, Folder 2)
- Speaking Invitations. C. (Box 381, Folder 3a-3c)
- Speaking Invitations. D-E. (Box 381, Folder 4)
- Speaking Invitations. F. (Box 381, Folder 5)
- Speaking Invitations. G. (Box 381, Folder 6)
- Speaking Invitations. H. (Box 381, Folder 7a-7b)
- Speaking Invitations. I. (Box 382, Folder 1)
- Speaking Invitations. J-L. (Box 382, Folder 2)
- Speaking Invitations. M. (Box 382, Folder 3)
- Speaking Invitations. N. (Box 382, Folder 4)
- Speaking Invitations. O-P. (Box 382, Folder 5)
- Speaking Invitations. T-V. (Box 382, Folder 6)
- Speaking Invitations. W-Z. (Box 382, Folder 7a-7b)
- T, 1962-1966 (Box 383, Folder 1)
  Incl. three letters from Norman Thomas, one criticizing D.D. & George Meany for their support of U.S. intervention in Dominican Republic, May 1965.
- T, 1950-1961 (Box 383, Folder 2a-2c)
- Thirty-five Hr. Week, 1953-1954 (Box 383, Folder 3)
  I.c.w. Union officers to enforce 35-hr. wk. clause in collective bargaining agreements.
- Trade Associations (T.A.), 1932-1966 (Box 383, Folder 3a)
  Divided into 1. Trade Assoc., New York. 2. Trade Assoc., Out-of-Town. Corres. bet. Union officers & assoc. on negotiations for agreement, labor-management, garment industry. Arranged alphabetically by assoc.
- T.A. New York. Affiliated Dress Mfrs. Assn., 1933-1960 (Box 383, Folder 4)
- T.A. Affiliated Ladies Apparel Carrier Assoc.; Associated Dress Carriers of Brooklyn and Queens, Inc., 1939-1940 (Box 383, Folder 5)
- T.A. Allied Underwear Assoc., 1935-1964 (Box 383, Folder 6)
- T.A. American Cloak and Suit Mfrs. Assoc., 1935-1954 (Box 383, Folder 7)
- T.A. Artificial Flower Assoc., 1947 (Box 383, Folder 8)
- T.A. Associated Corset and Brassiere Mfrs. of N.Y., 1933-1966 (Box 383, Folder 9a-9b)
- T.A. Associated Robe Mfrs., Inc., 1937-1938 (Box 383, Folder 10)
- T.A. Association of Knitted Fabric Mfrs., Inc., 1947 (Box 383, Folder 11)
- T.A. Belt Assoc., Inc., 1940 (Box 383, Folder 12)
- T.A. Children's Dress, Cotton Dress and Sportswear Contractors Assoc., Inc., 1934-1965 (Box 384, Folder 1)
  I.c.w. Assoc. re dispute w. Local 91.
- T.A. Cloak and Suit Trucking Assoc., Inc., 1937-1955 (Box 384, Folder 2)
- T.A. Cotton Apparel and Robe Producers' Assoc., Inc., 1956 (Box 384, Folder 3)
- T.A. Covered Button Assoc., Inc., 1940 (Box 384, Folder 4)
- T.A. Covered Button and Buckle Creators, Inc., 1937-1940 (Box 384, Folder 5)
- T.A. Embroidery Mfrs. Assoc. See Pleaters and Stitchers Mfrs. Assoc. (Box 384, Folder 6)
- T.A. Fashion Apparel Industry Assoc., 1965 (Box 384, Folder 7)
- T.A. Garment Center's Truck Owners Assoc., Inc., 1940-1950 (Box 384, Folder 8)
- T.A. Greater Blouse, Skirt and Neckwear Contractors Assoc., Inc., 1934-1963 (Box 384, Folder 9)
- T.A. House Dress Institute, 1961 (Box 384, Folder 10)
- T.A. Industrial Assoc. of Juvenile Apparel Mfrs., Inc., 1943-1963 (Box 384, Folder 11)
- T.A. Industrial Council of Cloak, Suit and Skirt Mfrs., Inc., 1951-1960 (Box 384, Folder 12)
- T.A. Industrial Council of Cloak, Suit and Skirt Mfrs., Inc., 1941-1950 (Box 384, Folder 13)
  Corres. w. Samuel Klein re Local 38, 1941-44.
- T.A. Infants' and Children's Coat Assoc., Inc., 1960-1966 (Box 384, Folder 14)
- T.A. Infants' and Children's Coat Assoc., 1943-1959 (Box 384, Folder 15a-15c)
  I.c.w. Charles Baker, Joseph Rubin of the Assoc. & Israel Feinberg, Isidore Nagler, Henoch Mendelsund of the Union on firms' applications to membership in Assoc.
- T.A. Infants' and Children's Coat Assoc., 1943-1959 (Box 385, Folder 1a-1c)
- T.A. Infants' and Children's Novelties Assoc., Inc., 1954-1959 (Box 385, Folder 2)
- T.A. Lingerie Mfrs. Assoc., 1933-1936 (Box 385, Folder 3)
- T.A. Mfrs. of Snow Suits, Novelty Wear and Infants' Coats, Inc., 1944 (Box 385, Folder 4)
- T.A. Merchants Ladies' Garment Assoc., Inc., 1941-1959 (Box 385, Folder 5)
  Corres. w. Joseph Dubow, Exec. Dir of Assoc.
- T.A. Miscellaneous Trade Assoc., 1965-1966 (Box 385, Folder 6)
- T.A. Nat'l. Assoc. of Blouse Manufacturers; 7 Inc., 1933-1959 (Box 385, Folder 7)
- T.A. Nat'l. Assoc. of House Dress Mfrs., Inc., 1949-1953 (Box 385, Folder 8)
- T.A. Nat'l. Assoc. of Shoulder Pad Mfrs., Inc., 1960 (Box 385, Folder 9)
- T.A. Nat'l. Assoc. of Women's and Children's Apparel Salesmen, Inc., 1965 (Box 385, Folder 10)
  I.c.w. Marshall J. Mantler (Exec. Dir.) re affiliation w. a labor union.
- T.A. Nat'l. Buttonhole Mfrs. Assoc., Inc., 1937 (Box 385, Folder 11)
- T.A. Nat'l. Dress Mfrs. Assoc., 1933-1960 (Box 385, Folder 12a-12b)
- T.A. Nat'l. Knitted Outwear Assoc., 1938-1939 (Box 385, Folder 13)
- T.A. Nat'l. Skirt Mfrs. Assoc., Inc., 1953 (Box 385, Folder 14a-14b)
  Corres. w. Martin L. Cohen (Mgr.), Local 105, Louis Reiss (Mgr.), Local 23 & Assoc. re Local jurisdictional dispute.
- T.A. Nat'l. Women's Neckwear and Scarf Assoc., 1933-1939 (Box 385, Folder 15)
- T.A. Negligee Mfrs. Assoc., 1938 (Box 385, Folder 16)
- T.A. N.Y. Coat and Suit Assoc., Inc., 1961-1964 (Box 386, Folder 1)
- T.A. N.Y. and New England Carriers Assoc., Inc., 1957 (Box 386, Folder 2)
- T.A. N.Y. Raincoat Mfrs. Assoc., Inc., 1942-1966 (Box 386, Folder 3)
- T.A. Plastic Products Mfrs. Assoc., Inc., 1937-1944 (Box 386, Folder 4)
- T.A. Pleaters, Stitchers and Embroidery Mfrs. Assoc., Inc., 1935-1965 (Box 386, Folder 5)
- T.A. Popular Price Dress Contractors Assoc., Inc., 1964 (Box 386, Folder 6)
- T.A. Popular-Priced Dress Mfrs. Group, Inc., 1935-1964 (Box 386, Folder 7a-7b)
- T.A. United Better Dress Mfrs. Assoc., 1945-1961 (Box 386, Folder 8)
- T.A. United Knitwear Mfrs. League, Inc., 1939-1960 (Box 386, Folder 9)
- T.A. United Popular Dress Mfrs. Assoc., Inc., 1940-1963 (Box 386, Folder 10)
- T.A. United Underwear Contractors Assoc., Inc., 1939 (Box 386, Folder 11)
- T.A. Women's Apparel Shoulder Pad Assoc., Inc., 1953-1957 (Box 386, Folder 12)
- T.A. Boston Associated Dress Mfrs. Assoc., 1946 (Box 386, Folder 13)
- T.A. Boston Coat and Suit Mfrs. Assoc., 1934-1948 (Box 386, Folder 14)
- T.A. Boston New England Clothing and Rainwear Mfrs. Assoc., 1942-1965 (Box 386, Folder 15)
- T.A. California Apparel Contractors Assoc., 1951 (Box 386, Folder 16)
- T.A. California Sportswear and Dress Assoc., Inc., 1947-1961 (Box 386, Folder 17a-17b)
- T.A. Chicago Assoc. of Dress Mfrs., 1937-1941 (Box 386, Folder 18)
- T.A. Chicago Cloak and Suit Mfrs. Assoc., 1955-1958 (Box 386, Folder 19)
- T.A. Chicago Dress Contractors Assoc., 1940-1945 (Box 386, Folder 20)
- T.A. Conn. Dress Mfrs. Assoc., 1933-1934 (Box 387, Folder 1)
- T.A. Fall River Needle Trades Employers Assoc., 1958 (Box 387, Folder 2)
- T.A. Fall River New England Apparel Mfrs. Assoc., Inc., 1958-1961 (Box 387, Folder 3)
- T.A. Florida Apparel Mfrs. Assoc., 1963 (Box 387, Folder 4)
- T.A. Illinois Garment Mfrs. Assoc., 1944 (Box 387, Folder 5)
- T.A. Los Angeles Associated Sportswear Mfrs. of L.A., 1939-1947 (Box 387, Folder 6)
- T.A. Los Angeles Coat and Suits Mfrs. Assoc., 1943-1966 (Box 387, Folder 7)
- T.A. Los Angeles West Coast Garment Mfrs. Assoc., 1949-1950 (Box 387, Folder 8)
- T.A. Minnesota Apparel Industries, 1949 (Box 387, Folder 9)
- T.A. Montreal Dress Mfrs. Guild, 1939-1940 (Box 387, Folder 10)
- T.A. New Jersey-Dress Mfrs. and Contractors Assoc., 1934-1965 (Box 387, Folder 11)
- T.A. N.J. Washable Dress Contractors Assoc., 1938-1958 (Box 387, Folder 12)
- T.A. Ohio-Apparel Mfrs. Assoc., 1940-1941 (Box 387, Folder 13)
- T.A. Pacific Coast Garment Mfrs., 1944-1954 (Box 387, Folder 14)
- T.A. Pennsylvania Affiliated Independent Dress Contractors Assoc., 1961-1962 (Box 387, Folder 15)
- T.A. Pa. Associated Independent Dressmakers of Pa., 1964 (Box 387, Folder 16)
- T.A. Pa. Dress Mfrs. Assoc., Inc., 1940-1953 (Box 387, Folder 17)
- T.A. Pa. Garment Mfrs. Assoc., Inc., 1959 (Box 387, Folder 18)
  Case of Assoc. & Union before NLRB, Nov. 1959.
- T.A. Pa. Slate Belt Apparel Contractors Assoc., Inc., 1959-1962 (Box 387, Folder 19a-19b)
- T.A. Pa. United Dress Mfrs. Assoc. of Pa., Inc., 1964 (Box 387, Folder 20)
- T.A. Philadelphia Blouse and Dress Contractors' Assoc., 1945 (Box 387, Folder 21)
- T.A. Philadelphia Coat and Suit Mfrs. Assoc., 1944-1953 (Box 387, Folder 22)
- T.A. Phila. Knitted Outwear Mfrs. Assoc., 1937-1940 (Box 387, Folder 23)
- T.A. Phila. Pleaters, Stitchers and Embroideries Assoc., 1936-1938 (Box 387, Folder 24)
- T.A. Phila. Waist and Dress Mfrs. Assoc., 1936-1952 (Box 387, Folder 25)
- T.A. Puerto Rico Coast and Brassiere Assoc., 1955-1965 (Box 387, Folder 26)
- T.A. St. Louis Associated Garment Industries, 1939-1952 (Box 387, Folder 27)
- T.A. Twin Cities Dress Mfrs. Assoc., 1938-1943 (Box 387, Folder 28)
- T.A. Toronto Cloak Mfrs. Assoc., 1937-1939 (Box 387, Folder 29)
- T.A. Toronto Dress Mfrs. Guild of Toronto, 1941-1948 (Box 387, Folder 30)
- T.A. Vancouver Cloak Mfrs. Assoc., 1946 (Box 387, Folder 31)
- T.A. Winnipeg Ladies' Garment Mfrs. Assoc., 1933-1937 (Box 387, Folder 32)
- Training Institute of Union, 1962-1963 (Box 388, Folder 1)
- Training Inst. of Union, 1957-1959 (Box 388, Folder 2a-2b)
  Corres. bet. Union officers & Gus Tyler; report by Tyler, Aug. 1958; applicants requesting admission to Inst.; assignments for graduates.
- Training Institute of Union, 1955-1956 (Box 388, Folder 3a-3c)
- Training Inst. of Union, 1953-1954 (Box 388, Folder 4a-4c)
- Training Inst. of Union, 1952 (Box 388, Folder 5)
- Training Inst. of Union, 1950-1951 (Box 389, Folder 1a-1c)
  Incl. minutes of GEB Education Comm. meeting, 1950; correspondence. on forming Training Inst.
- Triangle Fire Memorial, 1961 (Box 389, Folder 2a-2b)
  (50th Anniversary) Incl. D.D. address at Memorial meeting, March 1961; releases, invitations to attend Memorial; letters from Leon Stein.
- Truman, Harry S, 1944-1959 (Box 389, Folder 3)